Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-684. Rules. Texas and New Mexico Railroad
    - Case No. R-2820, 1953-1954 (Box 462, Folder 5)
      September 1953-54.
  - Sub-Series 279-686. Rules. Baines, N.H. (Concession, Union Depot, Portland, Oregon)
    - General, 1953 (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 462, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-687. Rules. Bauxite and Northern Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 462, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-688. Rules. Valdosta Southern Railway Company
    - General, 1954-1956 (Box 462, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-689. Rules. Western Maryland Warehouse Company
    - NLRB Case No. 5-RC-3129, 1960-1962 (Box 462, Folder 10)
    - NLRB Cases Nos. 5-CA-1720 and 5-CB-398, 1960-1962 (Box 462, Folder 11)
    - NLRB Case No. 5-CE-1, 1960-1962 (Box 462, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-2534 and R-3138, 1956-1957 (Box 462, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-690. Rules. Air France
    - Case No. R-2934, 1955-1956 (Box 462, Folder 14)
    - Case No. R-2934, 1956 (Box 462, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-693. Rules. Quebec, North Shore, and Labrador Railway Company
    - General, 1954 (Box 462, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-694. Rules. Chicago Heights Terminal Transfer Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 462, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-695. Rules. Live Oak, Perry, and Gulf Railroad Company
    - Union Shop, 1975-1958 (Box 462, Folder 18)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5120, 1956 (Box 462, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 462, Folder 20)
    - Mediation Case No. R-2985, 1955-1956 (Box 462, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-696. Rules. Wellsville, Addison, and Galeton Railroad
    - Mediation Case No. A-5100, 1956-1961 (Box 462, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-698. Rules. Roscoe, Snyder, and Pacific Railway
    - General, 1956 (Box 462, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-710. Rules. Koppers Company, Inc., Creosoting Plant, Point Reading, New Jersey
    - General, 1955-1962 (Box 462, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-711. Rules. New York Connecting Railroad
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 462, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 279-712. Rules. Suburban Station Building Corporation, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 462, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 279-712. Rules. Herman, Richard B.
    - General, 1960-1966 (Box 462, Folder 27)
    - Union Shop, 1957 (Box 462, Folder 28)
    - General, 1957-1959 (Box 462, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 279-713. Rules. Brownsville and Matamoros Bridge Company
    - Mediation Case No. A-5433, 1957 (Box 462, Folder 30)
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-2539 and R-3132, 1956-1957 (Box 462, Folder 31)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 462, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 279-716. Rules. Southern Pacific Building Company
    - General, 1965-1961 (Box 462, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 279-717. Rules. Gillette Motor Transport, Inc.
    - General, 1956 (Box 462, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 279-718. Rules. Allied Aviation Service Company (California)
    - General, 1958-1960 (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. C-3511, 1964-1965 (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case No. R-3278, 1957-1958 (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-721. Rules. Chestnut Ridge Railway Company
    - Mediation Case No. R-3155, 1957 (Box 463, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 279-722. Rules. Carey Transportation Company
    - Certification. Case No. 2-RC-9173, 1957 (Box 463, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 279-724. Rules. Asbury Rapid Transit System
    - General, 1957 (Box 463, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-728. Rules. International Air Services, Inc.
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-3248 and R-3555, 1962 (Box 463, Folder 7)
    - NMB Case No. C-2912, 1959 (Box 463, Folder 8)
    - Mediation Case No. R-3283, 1958 (Box 463, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 279-730. Rules. Republic Carloading and Distributing Company, Inc.
    - Case No. 13-CA-2925, 1958-1959 (Box 463, Folder 10)
    - Case No. 13-CA-2925, 1958 (Box 463, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-733. Rules. Louis Dreyfus Corporation
    - General, 1958-1961 (Box 463, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-734. Rules. Illinois Central Railroad Hospital Department
    - Mediation Case No. A-6606, 1960-1962 (Box 463, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 463, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 279-735. Rules. Western Pacific Railroad Company Medical Department
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 463, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 279-739. Rules. Riddell Airlines
    - Mediation Case No. R-3364, 1959 (Box 463, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-740. Rules. Trans-Caribbean Airways
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 463, Folder 17)
      1959-October 13, 1960.
    - Mediation Case No. A-6169, 1959-1961 (Box 463, Folder 18)
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-2895 and R-2247, 1959 (Box 463, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-741. Rules. Frisco Employees` Hospital Association
    - General, 1959-1961 (Box 463, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 279-742. Rules. Mackey Airlines
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-2921 and R-3385, 1959 (Box 463, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 279-743. Rules. Smith Airport Porter Service
    - Mediation Case No. 1959 (Box 463, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-747. Rules. Ward Sky Cap Porter Service
    - Mediation Cases Nos. C-2970 and R-3416, 1959-1960 (Box 463, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-748. Rules. KLM Royal Dutch Airlines
    - Mediation Case No. C-2098, 1953 (Box 463, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 279-781. Rules. Panama Airways NMB Cases Nos. C-3619, C-3631, R-3716, and R-3825
    - 1965-1966 (Box 463, Folder 25)